Downloaded from
Cyro.se
I think Amira's gonna do something.
He thinks you're planning
an attack at the school
with someone. He doesn't
know it's with me.
AMIRA: I told him I've
explained everything to you
and you believed it.
Did Drew believe it?
I knew you were lying to me.
He was the one you were texting?!
[grunting]
I was beginning to think this
was gonna happen without you.
REBECCA: The party asked
John to run four years ago.
He knew I couldn't track Bin-Khalid
and work on his campaign
at the same time.
Standing up for the
truth the way you did...
It's what I've been telling
the American people I'm gonna
do for them.
NILAA: You'll still take a hit.
Well, the hit I can take.
It's the not swinging back...
That's what bothers me.
There's a hit on whoever accessed
the Army Rangers' identities.
The computer that belongs to
Nilaa Mizrani.
My husband's campaign manager.
Isaac, we can't let him do this.
I want to talk to him.
ISAAC: To try to change his mind? Nah.
He gonna do what he gonna do.
You know the man you married.
- You are unbelievable.
- She's my brother's wife.
Like that would stop you
starting up with her again.
Don't get crazy.
Money ain't coming in like it was.
That's why I reached out to you
in the first place,
put this deal together.
If Isaac doesn't make it
back from this meeting,
wouldn't be a lot of tears.
Bin-Khalid's people... They found us.
They killed the rest of the squad.
There was a flash drive
containing a list of sleeper cells,
along with all the codes
to trigger their attacks.
- Are you saying Grimes still has it?
- He said he'll sell it
to the terrorists if we
don't give him want he wants.
Two million dollars.
Show up at the 7th Street
metro station in one hour.
You got to give me more time!
You get me the money, or
I call Bin-Khalid's men.
I took one of their phones.
Just tell me if the money's
at the police station, Rebecca.
Your source is right.
Metro PD made a drug
bust in Southeast D.C.
Recovered a little over
$4.6 million in cash.
CARTER: Just need to know
where the evidence lockers are.
REBECCA: This is crazy. You'll
never get out of there alive.
ANDY: Okay, feeding in the loops.
Go.
- We were pulled off-line.
- They know.
Keith, we're running an
operation. If you shut us...
You're not running anything!
Lock them in interrogation now.
Rebecca, can you hear me?!
[no audio]
Can anyone hear me?!
_
Rebecca respects you.
It's not about not trusting you.
She had no choice.
Once she confirmed you weren't
the breach, she was relieved.
Can I get some water?
It-it is so hot in
here. Are you not hot?
[sighs]: Oh, God.
His story syncs up with Rebecca's.
They could be covering for each other.
According to his autonomic indicators,
he's telling the truth.
Perp managed to get his hands on a gun.
He took Vernon and Bates hostage
before they could process him.
Who is he?
Name's Eric Carter.
MARX: Mr. Carter!
This is Commander George Marx.
Tell me if you can hear me.
I hear you fine.
But if you want your
men alive, you stay out!
MARX: Nobody's doing anything.
Let's just keep talking, okay?
Tell me what you want.
I'll see what I can do.
Mr. Carter?
What's on the other side of this wall?
It's only a matter of time
before they come busting
through that door.
Shut up.
Listen, whatever you think
you know about me, you don't.
My name is Eric Carter.
I'm a former Army Ranger,
working with the National
Counter-Terrorism Unit.
The guy that was on that phone...
He has a list of sleeper cells
that are waiting to be activated.
If I don't get this money to him,
he's gonna sell that
list to the terrorists,
and there will be attacks
all over this country.
Do you understand me?!
Yeah, right.
Please.
I need your help.
Why don't you open that door,
explain it to the captain?
I swear to you, there
is no time for that.
Behind that wall...
Damn it, Bates!
...there's a stairwell. It
leads to a maintenance room
and a door to the back of the building.
Yeah. Send it to HRT.
They're on their way over here now.
I went deeper into Carter's file.
Guy enlisted in the Army.
Did tours in Afghanistan and Yemen,
worked his way up to Special Forces.
Special Forces?
Yep.
[explosion]
[panting]
- Get me out of here.
- Yeah.
Bates.
- Bates! He's getting away!
- Move!
Get through that door now!
He's getting away!
Come on, this way.
Bates! Hurry!
Go, go, go!
- Carter's gone. He's got a gun.
- Cut him loose!
- OFFICER: Room clear!
- Go, go, go!
This way. Follow me. On me.
DANIELS: Dispatch, this
is Lieutenant Daniels.
I'm ordering an emergency lockdown.
An armed suspect, six-two,
African-American, has escaped custody.
He is ex-military, and he is
holding an officer hostage.
Out this way!
Is there another way out?
That terrorist thing...
It's for real, right?
Yes. It's real.
[panting] Listen, if I
don't get out of here,
a lot of people are gonna die.
There's another exit on the roof.
Move.
Move, move, move.
It's down this way. Oh!
Visual of suspect!
[grunts]
- Come here!
- Oh!
Lower your weapons!
- Lower your weapons!
- Carter!
- Lower your weapon!
- You lower your weapons!
Let the man go!
I will kill him!
- MARX: Carter!
- CARTER: Drop your guns!
- This ends now!
- I need to get out of here!
OFFICER: I have a shot.
- I have to get out of here!
- Stand down.
Stand down.
Lower your weapons.
I have Rebecca Ingram
from CTU.
She's explained everything.
She's on the line for you.
CARTER: Rebecca?
Thank God. Are you okay?
You tell me.
I'm here with Director Mullins at CTU.
We cleared him. He's not the leak.
Are you sure?
Yes, I am.
Now, he's up to speed on everything.
He knows you need to
get Grimes the money
as soon as possible,
so I'm gonna put him on.
Carter, the police are giving you
a vehicle and a comm package.
A CTU tac team will follow you
to your rendezvous with Grimes.
But they won't make any moves
until they confirm Grimes
has the list of sleepers.
No. Ben told me to come alone.
He spots anyone he even thinks
might be with the
government, he will bolt.
I'll make sure the
tac team stays hidden.
You're not hearing me.
Ben is counter-surveillance
trained, okay?
He's also very paranoid.
Carter, Grimes has already
gotten away from you once.
We can't let that happen again.
Eric, you and I were
operating alone because
we didn't know who we could trust.
Now we do. We have a better chance
of recovering the list with CTU's help.
All right, Carter, are we clear?
Yeah. I heard you.
DANIELS: Let's get you
down to motor pool.
Yeah.
Come on, let's go.
Mullins is about to brief everyone,
and last I looked,
you're still on shift.
[softly]: Thanks.
I need to apologize
for everything that happened.
We'll adjudicate this another time.
- Okay.
Look, I have to ask.
Nilaa Mizrani...
We know she's a leak.
I want to be the one to bring her in.
I keep having to remind you,
you don't work here anymore.
She's my husband's campaign manager.
Keith, it would be easier
for John if I do this.
Take Agent Fox with you.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
According to Carter,
the list of sleepers
is on a USB flash drive.
We can't move in until
we confirm Grimes has it.
Give me a second.
Andy.
I'm sorry I've been shutting you out.
Look, I'm not happy about
the way things ended.
Things didn't just end.
You ended them.
MULLINS: I need everyone
to close the projects
you're working on and listen up.
We've just received reliable intel
that sleeper cells
are preparing to launch
multiple terror attacks.
We don't know where or when.
Casualties could be extremely high.
This is a high-value threat assessment.
We don't have a lot of time.
Stay focused.
This operation just became
priority number one.
[siren wailing in distance]
So, Jerome's staying here
to look after Nicole, all right?
Since when you need my permission?
Aisha, look,
this business ain't never
been easy, all right?
But it's never been this hard neither.
If I've been taking it
out on you, I'm sorry.
[scoffs] Whatever.
Come on.
Don't be like that, all right?
[knocking]
Take us a half hour, at least,
to get cross town to Royo, bro.
Isaac.
I...
What?
It's nothing. We good.
A'ight.
What you looking at?
♪ ♪
So, she wasn't there to pray.
She-she went there to talk down some
crackpot imam, call him out.
Well, even if that's true,
do you trust the voters
to make that distinction?
I do.
Well, John, you're an optimist,
and that's your great
gift, but I'm telling you
that a lot of these
folks... Your major donors...
One out of five of
them's gonna jump ship
if you defend her on this.
I don't think so, Dad. I think
they'd appreciate my loyalty.
[sighs]
[phone ringing]
Oh, let me take this, it's Rebecca.
Ask her what she thinks.
I will.
Everyone's been asking
after you, darling.
I'm actually heading over there now.
Well, good.
John, you need to know...
Something's happened.
It's serious.
What's going on?
Secret Service is sequestering Nilaa.
They'll be discreet, but I
wanted to give you the heads-up.
Wait, wait, wh-what do
you mean, sequestering her?
I'll explain when I see you.
I'll be there in 15 minutes.
- DONOVAN: Rebecca...
- I promise I'll tell you everything,
but you need to stay away
from her until I get there.
Please.
[talking quietly]
[giggles]
[phone vibrating]
Eric?
Nicole.
Oh, my God.
Thank God you're all right.
I'm sorry I haven't
called you before now.
It's okay, as long as you're safe.
How are you?
I'm fine. I'm fine, baby.
Listen, this whole thing
with Ben is winding down,
and we cleared the guy running CTU.
Does that mean we can go home?
Soon. [sniffs]
I'm-a come get you, and...
we can start to put this
whole thing behind us. Okay?
Listen, Nicole...
...I know I haven't been hearing you.
And I know I got a lot of
things that I need to work on.
But I promise you,
I promise you things are
gonna be different. Okay?
I love you.
I love you, too.
I'll call you later.
Wait, Eric.
Yeah?
Isaac's girlfriend, or whatever she is,
she's up to something.
Like what?
I don't know. I don't know.
It's just a feeling I have
from how she's been acting.
And from a phone call she made
she didn't want me to hear.
I don't know, maybe
it's nothing, but, um,
you know, I'm worried about Isaac.
No, Isaac can take care
of hisself.
He is looking out for me.
Okay, listen, if... if
you can get her number
and tell me when she made that call,
CTU might be able to
pull up a transcript
or some kind of recording, okay?
They can do that?
They can do a lot of stuff
I didn't know they could.
Just make sure you tap into
all those surveillance cameras, okay?
[car approaching]
It's good to see you again, Carter.
I need a favor.
Phone call I need pulled for my wife.
- Those are the details.
- I'll get someone on it for you.
This is Agent Locke.
He's the best tactical
specialist in CTU.
He'll be leading the field team.
Now, we have no way of knowing
how Grimes will approach
you at the station.
We'll keep the bulk of the tac
team out of your line of sight.
Agent Locke will shadow you.
As long as he stays invisible.
Grimes won't see me.
We've just hot mic'd your phone.
We'll be able to hear
everything that's going on,
and we will not make any moves
till we confirm that Grimes
has the list with him.
Yeah, I'm due at the station.
Good luck.
Locke.
Look, I don't know what
your orders are, but, um,
I don't want Ben coming
out of this in a body bag.
That's up to him.
I'm just after the list.
So am I.
But Ben and I served together.
That makes us brothers.
No matter what he's done.
[engine starts]
You asked me to remotely
erase the memory.
I ran a locate on Malik
and Rashid's phones.
Also their guys, huh?
Five of the phones are here, stationary,
in police custody.
We lost six men, not five.
The sixth one is in motion.
Someone else has it.
It's either Grimes or Carter.
Whoever has that phone,
I'll get him myself,
so there will be no more mistakes.
[steady beeping]
[school bell ringing]
We wait until it's
dark before we move him.
This is bad.
We've stayed hidden
for two years, Amira.
And we stay that way as long
as we have to, I promise.
How's the teacher holding up?
He's fine.
'Cause killing someone
for the first time, it...
it's no small thing.
And we can't do this without him.
You understand, Amira?
_
You don't sound so sure.
Your brother was asking
about me, wasn't he?
Yes.
And what did you say?
I told him you're with us.
So don't make me a liar.
No, I absolutely agree with that, but...
Why don't you grab a bite to eat first.
I'll catch up with you outside.
Hmm? Thank you so much, both of you.
Okay, so tell me, what
the hell is going on?
John... this is the last thing
I want to be telling you.
The last thing you need to hear.
Someone used my proprietary
code to get into the CTU system.
They accessed the file
identifying the Rangers
who took out Bin-Khalid.
And now most of them are dead.
We ran a trace.
The file was accessed
from Nilaa's computer.
I don't...
Why would she do that?
I'm not sure yet.
But the upshot is: she may be
facilitating a terrorist attack
on domestic soil.
John.
Gage's campaign came
up with some evidence
linking Nilaa to a radical mosque.
I confronted her about it,
and she... she said she
was there to protest,
and I-I believed her.
I understand. You wanted to believe her.
She volunteered for
my first Senate race.
You know, she went from
working the phone banks
to running my campaign.
I'm sorry, John.
AGENT FOX: Excuse me, ma'am.
We're ready.
She's in here.
I had them set up video and audio
before they sequestered her.
Your guests are expecting you outside,
you should get back to them.
No. I-I need to see this.
Okay.
[sniffs]
[clears throat]
Do you know why I asked to talk to you?
I'm waiting for you to tell me.
Take a seat.
I'd rather stand.
Over the last few hours,
terrorists killed four of the
Rangers who took out Bin-Khalid.
This is a copy of my server log.
The highlighted subroutine
contains the wit-sec
information on those Rangers.
It was accessed 25 days ago
at 6:05 a.m. from your I.P. address.
Nilaa, we've known each other
a long time.
I don't want this to be
you, so help me understand.
Who are you working with?
First Gage tries linking
me to some radical mosque,
and now you're calling me a terrorist?
Well, it wasn't me.
You need to do better than that.
I wasn't at campaign headquarters then.
I take a run every morning
at 6:00, right after I pray.
I never miss either one when I'm in D.C.
Show me your route.
We'll see if we can confirm it.
[knocking on door]
GRACE: Mr. Harris?
You said I could come
by to go over my test.
She'll go away.
Not if she heard the faucet.
GRACE: Mr. Harris?
[knocking]
Hold on, I'm-I'm coming.
Wait!
Hey, Grace, uh, sorry,
I-I completely spaced.
I'm working with another,
uh, student right now.
So maybe we can do this tomorrow.
Are you all right, Mr. Harris?
Your hand.
Oh, I'm not, um...
I-I dropped a beaker.
[chuckles] I-I must've cut myself
cleaning it up.
It's nothing.
So, I'll see you tomorrow.
[lock clicks]
She could tell that I was lying to her.
- I don't think so.
- We have to get him out of here.
No, we need to wait until it's dark.
[coughing, panting]
[coughing]
[weakly]: He... hel...
[gasps]
Quick, before someone sees him.
My God.
What happened?
We don't know.
- We just saw him lying here.
- Yeah.
Help! Somebody help!
[students murmuring]
COACH: Something's going on over here.
COACH: Get on the phone, call 911.
DONOVAN: ...until my dad
sits me down after the game,
and-and he says, uh, "Son,
stopping at third base is
no better than striking out.
If you want to make a difference,
you got to bring it home."
[crowd cheering]
With your support in
November, we'll be...
Keep checking traffic cams,
surveillance from local businesses,
anything that could prove
Nilaa was out running
when she said she was.
Okay.
Henry.
So, you just slip in after
the party's already started,
and then disappear
behind closed doors without
so much as a "hello"?
- Hello.
- Mm.
- I'm sorry.
- Now, don't be sorry.
Just tell me what the hell's going on.
There was a situation at CTU.
And this, um, situation,
did it have something to do
with my son's campaign manager?
Henry, you know I can't talk about this.
I just found out she's under lockdown.
Do you honestly think I don't know
what's going on in my own house?
Now, Rebecca,
whatever is going on, if
it affects John's campaign,
you need to bring me up to speed.
[phones ringing, agents chattering]
Carter's two minutes out.
I've got eyes on sight.
[sighs]
Mullins asked me to pull
up a cell phone conversation
for Eric Carter's wife.
But I can't find it.
That's because NSA
hasn't captured it yet
from the phone company servers.
But, look, if we go
into the system directly
and I.D. the cell tower
that handled the call...
See?
So, um, what's going
on with you and Locke?
[chuckles]
He broke it off.
Thought if it got out,
it'd screw up his career.
Geez, what year is he living in?
But, you know, behind closed doors,
when promotions are being handed out,
it-it matters.
That's what Tom thinks, anyway.
There it is.
You can send it as
soon as it decompresses.
Thanks.
[phone vibrates]
_
Be right back.
AISHA [recorded]: Royo, it's me, Aisha.
ROYO: What's up?
I don't like the way
she been looking at me.
Maybe she knows something.
You want me to do her right now?
No.
Not until Royo calls and we
know Isaac's taken care of.
AISHA: I know you ain't
down with the split,
never have been, maybe I can do better.
- ROYO: You?
- AISHA: That's why I reached out to you
in the first place,
put this deal together.
If Isaac doesn't make it
back from this meeting,
wouldn't be a lot of tears.
Something wrong?
No. I just, um, I had
to make a phone call.
To who?
You're supposed to be laying low.
Why don't you give me that.
[chuckles]
You serious?
Something wrong?
No.
Carter's entering the station now.
[man speaking indistinctly over P.A.]
[line ringing]
BEN: Yeah.
Ben, I'm here.
Where are you?
Platform number two.
Stay on the line.
We have facial rec looking for Grimes
on traffic and security cams.
So far no match.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Ben.
What now, man?
Get on the train.
[electronic bell chimes]
[train doors close]
Go, go. Go, go!
[tires screeching]
All right, man, listen, I'm here.
I'm on the train. Where are you, Ben?
Where are you?
BEN: Right here.
But you're staying right there.
Ben, I got your money.
Just give me the list and we're done.
I've got eyes on Grimes.
- Any sign of the list?
- Not yet.
Ben, we had a deal.
Ben,
the list.
I'm taking you to it.
For now, you stay right where you are.
They said he's stable.
- That's it. We got to get out of here.
- What?
The second he wakes up, he'll
tell them about us, everything.
And what do you think my
brother would say about that?
[sighs] W-We don't have a choice.
Yes, we do.
I go to the hospital, and
I can try to finish this.
Go back and finish the
compound. My brother's waiting.
Excuse me, excuse me.
I'm his girlfriend.
I'd like to travel with
him to the hospital.
- Climb in.
- Okay.
[ambulance engine starts]
[doors close]
[siren wailing]
There were no cameras along your route.
No way to confirm you were out
running when you said you were.
But I was.
I had the CTU search for any cameras
near the campaign headquarters.
There's a bank in the building.
The ATM camera picked up a reflection
from the lobby window.
You said you were out
running that morning.
But here you are, entering the office
moments before your
computer was used to access
the Rangers' new identities.
You lied, Nilaa.
No.
- No, that's not me.
- You need to come clean.
Tell me who you're working
with, and I will do my best
to take the death penalty off the table,
because that is what the
A.G. will be asking for.
I'm telling the truth! I didn't do it!
That's not me!
That's not me.
Very nice. Smile.
[phone beeps]
_
DONOVAN: I so appreciate you coming.
- Thank you. No problem.
- God bless.
- Here we go.
- [camera clicks]
Talk to me.
My guy was able to hack the ATM camera,
change the time stamp.
Rebecca's already pulled the footage,
and she has a record that Nilaa
was at campaign headquarters
when her file was breached.
And there are no other cameras?
There's no way that CTU
can confirm Nilaa's story?
I went over the route myself, twice.
CTU won't be able to
trace the leak back to you.
That's what you said the first time.
Henry, you asked me to handle your mess.
I'm handling it.
[exhales]
Giving up those soldiers was bad enough.
Now Nilaa.
It's our only play.
Unless you're ready to
burn down John's campaign
and everything that you spent
your life trying to build.
[quietly]: Target's
moving towards Carter.
Copy that.
You wearing a wire?
I'm not wired, man.
He's not with me.
I came alone, man.
Just like you asked me to.
Sit.
[bag zips]
I didn't want it to go like this,
but I didn't have a choice.
You did have a choice.
You could've turned the list
in with me and walked away.
No, no.
That's what this is all about.
It's about trying to get
away from them, for good.
What do you think I got the money for?
Eric...
...I got a plan.
Listen, a guy... a guy
that I know went here.
They got these lakes made by glaciers.
They're deep and ice-cold.
It's like a shock to your system.
You ever swim in glacier water?
[sniffs]
No.
I always thought I could settle
down in a place like this.
[sniffs] Looks like a nice place, Ben.
Then you should come. You should come.
You should bring Nicole. You
two could get a fresh start.
There are no fresh starts, man.
You still got to deal with yourself.
No matter where you go.
I didn't mean to drag you into this.
But I just, I knew I
couldn't do it on my own.
"Never shall I fail my comrades."
You remember those words?
MULLINS: Get ready. They're
approaching the next station.
We're almost there.
This might be it.
Copy that.
[electronic bell chimes]
AUTOMATED VOICE [over P.A.]: Step back.
Doors closing.
Step back.
LOCKE: They're heading to the mezzanine.
Copy that.
Linking you into the
station's camera network.
Uploading station schematics now.
Turn in, right here, right here.
[tires screeching]
No good cover on the mezzanine.
We need to deploy outside the station.
Entry points here and here.
[man speaking indistinctly over P.A.]
All right, give me the money.
Where's the list?
You heard me, Eric.
No angle here. Is he
retrieving the list?
That's my bet.
Will confirm as soon as I have eyes on.
I have four potential hostiles.
I need to warn Carter.
Go!
Let's go, boys. Go!
MAN: He's got a gun!
- LOCKE: Carter!
- [woman screams, gunfire]
You lied to me!
[men shouting]
Check on them, make sure
they're okay. Her, too.
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
Down the stairs.
[groans]
BEN: I'm fine. They got the list.
Carter, where are you?
The hostiles have the list.
I'm headed into the tunnel.
Carter, we didn't catch that. Say again.
They just entered the exit stairwell.
Confirm you're getting this!
[train horn blows]
♪ ♪
[sirens wailing in distance]
[car horn honking]
[people murmuring]
MAN: Get out of the street!
[horns honking, tires screeching]
[people shouting]
[car horn honking]
[phone ringing]
Talk to me.
The terrorists, they...
they got away with the list.
[sirens wailing]
[tires screech]
For more new Episodes go to
Cyro.se